Finding Aid for the Colonial Court Records Group, 1665-1787 SR.401
State Archives of North Carolina
- Estate Papers, 1665-1767; SR.401.8; 5.000; Colonial Courts (Box Estate Papers, Adams-Branston, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Brasely-Child, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Church-Eaves, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Edgerton-Haughton, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Hawkins-Hyde, 1665-1767, Box Estate
  - Rowlison (Rollison), William, 1714-1715; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Rowlison (Rollison), William)
  - Rushmore, Charles, 1700; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Rushmore, Charles)
  - Ryan, Thomas, 1755-1757; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Ryan, Thomas)
  - Ryley, John, Sr., 1737-1738; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Ryley, John, Sr.)
  - Salter, Edward (see also Josiah Clapham), 1734-1742; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Salter, Edward (see also Josiah Clapham))
  - Sanders, Priscilla (minor), 1738-1739; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Sanders, Priscilla (minor))
  - Sanderson, Basill, 1722; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Sanderson, Basill)
  - Sanderson, Richard, 1736-1744; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Sanderson, Richard)
  - Sanderson, Richard, Sr., 1718-1721; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Sanderson, Richard, Sr.)
  - Sarson, Lawrence, 1742-1746; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Sarson, Lawrence)
  - Scarborough, Augustus, 1710; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Scarborough, Augustus)
  - Scolley, Samuel, 1757; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Scolley, Samuel)
  - Scot, John, 1731; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Scot, John)
  - Scot, Joseph, 1751-1756; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Scot, Joseph)
  - Scott, Edward, 1742-1743; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Scott, Edward)
  - Shirley, James, 1737-1742; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Shirley, James)
  - Simons, John, 1728-1742; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Simons, John)
  - Simons, Mathew, 1701; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Simons, Mathew)
  - Simpson, William, n.d.; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Simpson, William)
  - Skinner, Richard, 1727-1728; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Skinner, Richard)
  - Slatter, Thomas, 1738-1744; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Slatter, Thomas)
  - Slaughter, Michael, 1740-1745; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Slaughter, Michael)
  - Slaughter, Thomas, 1702-1744; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Slaughter, Thomas)
  - Slocum, John, n.d.; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Slocum, John)
  - Slocum, Samuel, 1714; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Slocum, Samuel)
  - Small,, John, 1736-1742; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Small,, John)
  - Small, William, 1743-1745; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Small, William)
  - Smith, Edward, 1737-1739; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Smith, Edward)
  - Smith, John, 1732-1744; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Smith, John)
  - Smith, Robert, 1690; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Smith, Robert)
  - Smith, Phillip, 1744-1745; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Smith, Phillip)
  - Smithson, John, 1724-1725; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Smithson, John)
  - Smithweck, Hugh, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Smithweck, Hugh)
  - Snell, John, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Snell, John)
  - Snoad, John, 1743-1744; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Snoad, John)
  - Snowden, Christopher, 1759; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Snowden, Christopher)
  - Snowden (Snoden), Thomas, 1715-1723; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Snowden (Snoden), Thomas)
  - Sothel, Seth and Ann (Lear); Col. John Lear (3 estates), 1692-1705; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sothel, Seth and Ann (Lear); Col. John Lear (3 estates))
  - Sparnon, Joseph, 1718-1720; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sparnon, Joseph)
  - Sparrow, Thomas, 1724; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sparrow, Thomas)
  - Speight (Spight), John, 1741-1742; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Speight (Spight), John)
  - Speight, Moses, 1745; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Speight, Moses)
  - Speight, Thomas and Mary, 1737-1759; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Speight, Thomas and Mary)
  - Spence, David, 1742-1743; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Spence, David)
  - Spencer, John, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Spencer, John)
  - Spruill, Godfrey, 1702; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Spruill, Godfrey)
  - Standen, Edward, 1744-1759; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Standen, Edward)
  - Standin, William, 1745; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Standin, William)
  - Standing, Edward, 1748; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Standing, Edward)
  - Steele, John, Capt., n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Steele, John, Capt.)
  - Steele, William, 1721-1725; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Steele, William)
  - Steely (Staebs?), William, 1710-1715; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Staebs (Steele?), William)
  - Stoneham, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Stoneham, Thomas)
  - Steward, John, 1694-1695; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Steward, John)
  - Stuart, John, 1737-1739; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Stuart, John)
  - Stubbs, Thomas, 1739; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Stubbs, Thomas)
  - Sullivan, Daniel, 1729; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sullivan, Daniel)
  - Summerrell, Thomas, 1742-1744; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Summerrell, Thomas)
  - Summer, John, 1757-1758; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Summer, John)
  - Sutton, George, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sutton, George)
  - Sutton, Joseph, 1723; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sutton, Joseph)
  - Sutton, Nathaniel, 1704; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Sutton, Nathaniel)
  - Swall, John, 1740; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Swall, John)
  - Swann, Samuel, Maj., 1707-1712; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Swann, Samuel, Maj.)
  - Swann, Thomas, 1739-1745; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Swann, Thomas)
  - Talbot, Benjamin, 1746; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Talbot, Benjamin)
  - Tanner, Walter, 1703-1714; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Tanner, Walter)
  - Tanyhill, John, 1735-1742; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Tanyhill, John)
  - Tarper, Richard, 1744; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Tarper, Richard)
  - Taylor, Ebenezer, Rev., 1722; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Taylor, Ebenezer, Rev.)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel, 1735; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Taylor, Nathaniel)
  - Taylor, Thomas, 1758-1759; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Taylor, Thomas)
  - Tenner, James, 1735; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Tenner, James)
  - Thomas, Morgan, 1706-1707; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Thomas, Morgan)
  - Thorne, William, 1740-1742; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Thorne, William)
  - Thurrell, William, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Thurrell, William)
  - Thurston, John, n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Thurston, John)
  - Timberman, Gasper, 1721-1725; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Timberman, Gasper)
  - Todd, Robert, 1748-1758; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Todd, Robert)
  - Tomlin, (?) (minor), n.d.; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Tomlin, (?) (minor))
  - Took, James, 1714-1735; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Took, James)
  - Travis, Edward, 1745; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Travis, Edward)
  - Travis, William, 1697; CCR 206; Colonial Courts (Folder Travis, William)
  - Trotter, James, 1753-1758; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Trotter, James)
  - Trowel, Joseph, 1735; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Trowel, Joseph)
  - Trumbale, Symon, n.d.; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Trumbale, Symon)
  - Tuniclift, William, 1743-1744; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Tuniclift, William)
  - Underhill, Edward, 1758-1759; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Underhill, Edward)
  - Vans, John, 1745-1748; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Vans, John)
  - Vaughan, William, 1726-1727; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Vaughan, William)
  - Vince, William (orphan), 1726; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Vince, William (orphan))
  - Vinson, William, 1704; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Vinson, William)
  - Waad (Wade), Edward, 1691-1692; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Waad (Wade), Edward)
  - Walker, Edward and Margaret (minors), 1735; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Walker, Edward and Margaret (minors))
  - Walker, Henderson, 1705; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Walker, Henderson)
  - Walker, John, 1713-1745; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Walker, John)
  - Wallace, James, 1741-1759; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wallace, James)
  - Wallis, Robert, n.d.; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wallis, Robert)
  - Walton, Thomas, 1759; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Walton, Thomas)
  - Ward, Francis, 1697; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Ward, Francis)
  - Ward, Michael and James Sumner, 1757; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Ward, Michael and James Sumner)
  - Wardroper, Thomas, 1737-1738; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wardroper, Thomas)
  - Waters, Joseph, 1739-1743; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Waters, Joseph)
  - Waters, William, 1741; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Waters, William)
  - Watkin, Davis, 1744; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Watkin, Davis)
  - Watson, John, 1752-1759; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Watson, John)
  - Webb, Zacheriah, 1761; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Webb, Zacheriah)
  - Weldon, Benjamin, 1756; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Weldon, Benjamin)
  - Weldon, Poynes, 1744-1745; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Weldon, Poynes)
  - Welsh, John, 1737; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Welsh, John)
  - Wensley, Henry, 1741-1745; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wensley, Henry)
  - West, Benjamin, n.d.; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder West, Benjamin)
  - West, Dinah (minor), 1743-1744; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder West, Dinah (minor))
  - West, Samuel, n.d.; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder West, Samuel)
  - West, Thomas, 1722; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder West, Thomas)
  - Westbere, Charles, 1741; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Westbere, Charles)
  - Wharton, David, 1712; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wharton, David)
  - Wheatly, Benjamin, 1757-1759; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wheatly, Benjamin)
  - Wheatly, Samuel, 1740-1742; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wheatly, Samuel)
  - Whitbey, Richard and Deborah (minors), 1702; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Whitbey, Richard and Deborah (minors))
  - Wheeler, Joseph, 1744-1745; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wheeler, Joseph)
  - White, Ebenezer, 1715; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder White, Ebenezer)
  - White, Thomas, 1697; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder White, Thomas)
  - White, William, 1723-1726; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder White, William)
  - Wilkins, Charles, 1737; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilkins, Charles)
  - Wilkinson, William, 1706-1707; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilkinson, William)
  - Williams, Ayliff, 1734-1745; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Williams, Ayliff)
  - Williams, Lewis, 1722; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Williams, Lewis)
  - Williams, Rich, n.d.; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Williams, Rich)
  - Williams, William, 1736-1744; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Williams, William)
  - Williamson, Richard, 1696; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Williamson, Richard)
  - Willowby, John, n.d.; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Willowby, John)
  - Wilson, Caleb, 1755-1758; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilson, Caleb)
  - Wilson, Isaac, 1709-1720; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilson, Isaac)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1696; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilson, Robert)
  - Wilson, Samuel, 1722; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilson, Samuel)
  - Wilson, William, 1745-1746; CCR 207; Colonial Courts (Folder Wilson, William)
  - Winsley, Henry, 1743; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Winsley, Henry)
  - Winterbottom, Joseph, 17351737; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Winterbottom, Joseph)
  - Woodard, Samuel, 1755-1767; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Woodard, Samuel)
  - Woodard, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Woodard, Thomas)
  - Workman, Arthur, n.d.; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Workman, Arthur)
  - Worley, John, 1741-1743; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Worley, John)
  - Wright, Charles, 1700-1701; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Wright, Charles)
  - Wright, John, 1698; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Wright, John)
  - Yeoman, John, 1740; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Yeoman, John)
  - Young, Joseph, 1728; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Young, Joseph)
  - Young, Peter, 1743-1745; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Young, Peter)
  - Miscellaneous Estates, 1700-1744; CCR 208; Colonial Courts (Folder Miscellaneous Estates)
- Land Papers and Wills, 1665-1753; SR.401.9; 0.400; Colonial Courts (Box Land Papers and Wills, 1665-1753)
  The series is arranged by subject. Wills are arranged alphabetically by last name.
  This series contains documents relating to land. Land papers include bills of sale, deed records including part of a Deed Book, wills, bills of sale relating to Roanoke Island (1676- 1727), leases and land grants, civil actions concerning land, lists of headrights', good titles and ejectments, inventory and receipts from Brompton, Gabriel Johnston's plantation, individual wills, and one guardian record.
  - Land Grants, 1700-1721; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Land Grants)
  - Headrights, 1680-1704; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Headrights)
  - Good Titles and Ejectments, 1723-1746; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Good Titles and Ejectments)
  - Lists of Acreage, 1697-1720; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Lists of Acreage)
  - Deeds, Wills and Bills of Sale pertaining to the Island of Roanoke, 1676-1727; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Deeds, Wills and Bills of Sale pertaining to the Island of Roanoke)
  - Deeds and Bills of Sales (Part of Deed Book 1701-1703), 1689-1742; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Deeds and Bills of Sales (Part of Deed Book 1701-1703))
  - Lease of Land, 1701-1728; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Lease of Land)
  - Land Survey, 1704-1743; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Land Survey)
  - Petitions and Agreements, 1697-1736; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Petitions and Agreements)
  - Civil Cases and Bonds, 1685-1753; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Civil Cases and Bonds)
  - Civil Cases Involving Sale of Land, 1719-1744; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Civil Cases Involving Sale of Land)
  - Land Rights Suit, Peyton vs. Campain, 1729-1736; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Land Rights Suit, Peyton vs. Campain (1729-1736))
  - Inventory and Receipts of Brompton (Gabriel Johnston Plantation), 1740-1751; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Inventory and Receipts of Brompton (Gabriel Johnston Plantation))
  - Mathew Rowan vs Henry McCulloh (Expenses Incurred Surveying Bladen and New Hanover Counties), 1744-1746; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Mathew Rowan vs Henry McCulloh (Expenses Incurred Surveying Bladen and New Hanover Counties))
  - Miscellaneous, 1696-1721; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Miscellaneous)
  - Harris, Thomas (will), 1665; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Harris, Thomas (will))
  - Hassold, Thomas (will), 1696; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Hassold, Thomas (will))
  - Reed, Andrew (will), 1728; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Reed, Andrew (will))
  - Simons, John (will), 1731; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Simons, John (will))
  - Tully, Cornelius (will), 1709; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder Tully, Cornelius (will))
  - West, Robert (will), 1689; CCR 209; Colonial Courts (Folder West, Robert (will))
- Taxes and Accounts, 1679-1759; SR.401.10; 0.600; Colonial Courts (Box Taxes and Accounts)
  This series is arranged by subject and tax lists are arranged by year and/or county.
  This series contains documents pertaining to county taxes and accounts. Materials include claims, tithables, quite rents, corn lists, tax lists and personal and public accounts. Tithables and tax lists pertain to the counties of Currituck, Craven, Chowan, Granville, Northhampton, Beaufort, Pasquotank, Perquimans, and Bertie.
  - Claims, 1713-1720; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Claims)
  - Personal Accounts, 1691-1698; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Personal Accounts, 1700-1709; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Personal Accounts, 1710-1719; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Personal Accounts, 1720-1729; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Personal Accounts, 1730-1739; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Personal Accounts, 1740-1745; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Personal Accounts, n.d.; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Personal Accounts)
  - Public Accounts, 1683-1759; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Public Accounts)
  - Quit-Rents, 1679; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Quit-Rents)
  - Tithables, 1692-1694; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables)
  - Tithables, 171-1722; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables)
  - Tithables: Chowan Co. (see also Tax Lists: Chowan Co.), 1719-1753; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables: Chowan Co. (see also Tax Lists: Chowan Co.))
  - Tithables: Currituk Co (see also Tax Lists: Currituck Co.), 1715-1751; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables: Currituk Co (see also Tax Lists: Currituck Co.))
  - Tithables: Craven, Granville, and Northhampton Co.; Beaufort Precinct, 1715-1755; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables: Craven, Granville, and Northhampton Co.; Beaufort Precinct)
  - Tithables: Pasquotank Co., 1714-1719; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables: Pasquotank Co.)
  - Tithables: Perquimans Co., 1702-1712; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tithables: Perquimans Co.)
  - Corn Lists, 1715-1716; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Corn Lists)
  - Tax Lists, Bertie Co., 1751-1754; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists, Bertie Co.)
  - Tax Lists: Chowan Co., 1714-1719; CCR 210; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists: Chowan Co.)
  - Tax Lists: Currituck Co., 1715-1721; CCR 211; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists: Currituck Co.)
  - Tax Lists: Pasquotank Co., 1712-1748; CCR 211; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists: Pasquotank Co.)
  - Tax Lists: Perquimans Co., 1713-1754; CCR 211; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists: Perquimans Co.)
  - Tax Lists: Tyrrell Co., 1754; CCR 211; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists: Tyrrell Co.)
  - Tax Lists and Tithables Miscellaneous, CCR 211; Colonial Courts (Folder Tax Lists and Tithables Miscellaneous)
- Jury Papers and Correspondence, 1676-1760; SR.401.11; 0.600; Colonial Courts (Box Jury Papers and Correspondence, 1676-1760)
  This series is arranged by subject and date.
  This series contains documents relating to the jury as well as correspondence. Included are jury lists, jury papers, grand jury presentments, jury lists, jury tickets, correspondence, and notes and receipts.
  - Jury List, 1740; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1742; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1745; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1746; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1747; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1748; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1749; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury List, 1755; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury List)
  - Jury Papers, 1713-1729; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury Papers)
  - Jury Papers, 1730-1740; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury Papers)
  - Jury Papers, 1741-1745; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury Papers)
  - Jury Papers, 1746-1754; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury Papers)
  - Jury Papers, n.d.; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury Papers)
  - Jury Tickets, 1756-1759; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Jury Tickets)
  - Grand Jury Presentments, 1700-1732; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Grand Jury Presentments)
  - Letters, 1676-1699; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Letters)
  - Letters, 1700-1709; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Letters)
  - Letters, 1710-1719; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Letters)
  - Letters, 1720-1739; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Letters)
  - Letters, n.d.; CCR 212; Colonial Courts (Folder Letters)
  - Letters and Copies To and From Governors, 1690-1756; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Letters and Copies To and From Governors)
  - Notes and Receipts, 1676-1687; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Notes and Receipts)
  - Notes and Receipts, 1690-1699; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Notes and Receipts)
  - Notes and Receipts, 1700-1710; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Notes and Receipts)
  - Notes and Receipts, 1711-1719; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Notes and Receipts)
  - Notes and Receipts, 1720-1739; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Notes and Receipts)
  - Notes and Receipts, 1740-1760; CCR 213; Colonial Courts (Folder Notes and Receipts)